The princess is wavering...
like a fruit, falling from a gentle breeze.
I'll leave it to you to give her a push in the right direction.
Understood?
Of course.
Please leave everything to us, Prince Hibiki.
I am unaccustomed to waiting.
We'll need to take drastic measures with her.
Cera.
Leika.
Britney.
Tyna.
CeLeBriTy 4!
Run! Summer Dream Grand Prix!
This is the PriPara News.
It's time for the long awaited event:
the Summer Idol Grand Prix!
Among its numerous entries,
a popular Top Class team ranked
above even the Major Class...
has submitted their entries from overseas.
It seems they decided to participate at the last moment!
Coming all the way from EuroPara, it's CeLeBriTy 4!
I wonder who will become their fifth member.
Whoever it is, I have no doubt they'll
become a fan favorite in no time!
Huh?!
From another country?
Top idols?
My prince is expecting great things of me.
But do I really want to be the princess?
Oh no! You've been staring like that for a while-tori!
Fuwari, you've become an egomaniac-tori!
No way! It's CeLeBriTy 4!
They're the Summer Dream's special guests!
They're so stylish!
Nice to meet you, Fuwari.
Who are you?
We're Celebrity 4.
Prince Hibiki has scouted us to ensure
your victory in the Summer Dream.
Huh?
My prince did?
Wow, you're so pretty.
So you're the princess he chose, huh?
Now then, team up with us.
Become elegant, and then gorgeous!
Do you all know him?
Of course.
Prince Hibiki's wish is our command!
And we've vowed to...
make Prince Hibiki's ideals a reality!
They're stunning...
Does this mean my prince is talking
with girls other than me?
Fuwari?
Who're these girls? What's going on-tori?
A hayseed like yourself should feel
honored to get to team up with us.
There you have it.
Now, let's like, go submit our entry right away.
U-Um...
I'm not really sure I want to become a princess.
There's no need to worry, little miss Fuwari.
If you're with us, you'll naturally acquire
the class of an urban débutante.
Even if you are just some country hick.
I'm sure we can become gorgeous friends.
Yeah.
Our victory is assured.
The others are all low ranking small fries.
Let's use them as stepping stones and shine above them!
Become elegant, and then gorgeous!
How dare you say such things about Toriko's idol!
Gorgeous and elite...
Is my prince looking for a princess
who's like these girls?
Fuwari is—
Shut it!
Toriko!
Salt?
Tare?
Onions?
Thank you...
Thanks to you four, I've made my decision.
I've decided I don't want to be a princess.
Therefore, I will not be forming a team with you.
W-Wait!
Hold it right there!
Would it upset you if I decided
not to become the princess?
Toriko will still love your songs
even if you aren't a princess-tori.
Thank you, Toriko.
Stop!
Laala!
Fuwari!
Perfect timing.
We were just looking for you.
We want you to join our team.
No, she'll be joining our team...
Laala, Sion, Dorothy, Reona...
I'd like to form a team with you four.
Huh?
What?!
I finally understand what I really want.
I'm best being Fuwari from the Palps.
You taught me that it was okay to be myself.
That's why I want to sing with the four of you!
Fuwari...
Tori!
I knew it'd end up like this.
Naturally, I have no objections.
I'd be glad to!
W-Wait a minute-pri!
You can't do that-pri.
SoLaMi Smile has always been together-pri!
You don't want to sing with us, Laala?
No, that's not true...
What should I do?
Hey, keep your eyes on the road!
Back up! Back up!
You're terrible!
Quit backseat driving!
Fuwari!
Don't run off like that!
Now we're all sad because of you!
What the heck are you doing?!
Are you okay?
This is way overkill-pri.
Shut your trap and mind your own business!
Huh?
You guys were on the news earlier.
It's CeLeBriTy 4!
Now then, little Fuwari, let's go submit our entry.
Entry?!
Even CeLeBriTy 4 wants Fuwari to join them-pri?!
I'm not joining you.
I'm teaming up with these four.
Well, about that...
Come now, you're totally joking, right?
With such low ranked girls?
Even if you have no chance of winning?
Excuse me?
Just 'cuz you're rich and famous,
doesn't mean you get to be a jerk!
What'd you say?!
If you're looking for a fight, I'll give you one!
Even though we'll make you shine the brightest,
you're just going to throw the chance away?
We're like, saying it's for your own good.
I guess we've got no choice.
You're coming with us.
Hold on.
What are you doing-tori?!
You don't have the option to refuse!
Stop-tori!
Slice in two!
It's extremely boorish to force someone
into something they don't want!
We won't let Fuwari fall into your hands!
That's right! Clock it!
You small fry idols think you stand a chance against us?!
Gorgeous!
Pri!
Fuwari, why won't you just come with us?
What should we do-tori?
Run!
Capisce!
Gorgeous!
Let's get out of here-tori!
Toriko will stay behind-tori.
Toriko will only bring misfortune-tori.
Fuwari, you'd better make it out alive-tori!
Give it up already!
I'm not cut out for this.
They've already crossed the river.
There's a bridge!
Lucky!
So Shikyouin is the one who called CeLeBriTy 4.
Are you really giving up on becoming a princess?
Yes, I've made up my mind.
Huh? Toriko's not here.
I wonder where she went.
Gorgeous Attack!
Mirei!
Sophy!
Pushuu...
This way!
Good idea.
Hey! Block heads!
What'd you say?!
P-Pushuu.
Sophy!
You're hurt, aren't you, Mirei?
It's nothing-pri.
Mirei!
Don't push yourself. You need to take care of your legs.
You won't be able to dance if you're hurt.
Let's see...
I found some medicinal herbs.
What are you doing?
What are you doing-pri?
Here.
Disinfecting it with this will keep the swelling down.
Thank you-pri.
We've already gone pretty far-pri.
The Grand Prix will be starting soon...
We better hurry or we're not gonna be able to enter.
We won't make it in time-pri.
Don't worry, we have plenty of time.
Everyone wants to hear our song.
Really?
Don't lose hope.
Let's sing together.
That was awesome!
We lost them somehow.
Yeah.
You're too heavy!
Come on!
What'd you say?!
What happened?
Are you injured?
Laala, go on without us.
Really?
Leave Sophy to me!
Show them the best five-person show
on behalf of Sophy and me-pri!
But—
Fuwari, Sion, and the rest, go out and do your best!
Make sure to take care of Laala-pri!
You have my word.
Sure.
Do your best!
Sophy...
Capisce!
Summer Dream Idol Grand Prix!
As all the hopefuls aiming to
be in the PriPara Dream Parade arrive,
the first round of the four Grand Prix
is underway.
The five members of the winning team...
will be entered as candidates to be the princesses
who will stand at the front of the parade.
Which team will become the stars of summer?
Without further ado,
let's get this started!
Hey, you sure this is the right path?
Don't worry.
The wind flow, direction of the sun,
and that bird over there all say we'll be fine.
Don't think you could just leave us behind!
They're still after us?
They're relentless!
Psychic power at maximum!
Strike-panda!
Summer bowling-panda!
Huh?!
Another one?!
That one's in the gutter for sure-panda.
Jump!
W-We're being swept down the river!
No way!
Driftwood!
Grab on!
Laala.
H-Hey, anyone else getting a bad feeling?
Bad feeling?
Of course there's a waterfall!
Serves you right!
Just let yourselves be washed down stream!
Fuwari, just give up on those girls—
Gorgeous!
What'd they come here for...
Don't!
Don't let go!
Everyone hold on tight!
Hold on tight!
Fuwari!
Girls!
Don't dare let go, you two!
Dorothy!
It's not like I want to let go!
Fuwari!
Do your best, everyone!
If you say so, Dorothy!
No letting go!
There's no way I'll let go...
of my friends!
That's right.
After traveling so far and meeting all of you,
we have to perform together as friends!
Congratulations!
A Dream Team has been born!
We've formed a Dream Team!
Hooray!
Let's see, our team name is...
Um...
Dressing Flower!
That's awesome!
Fuwari!
Toriko was really, really worried about you,
so she came to find you-tori!
How'd we get here?
To think that it led here...
Wasn't it kind of like an action-packed adventure?
Huh?!
Is that something a princess would say?
You really are a nature girl at heart.
We saw the natural splendor...
Please scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your coord.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Coord Change Start!
On top of the poppin' explorer outfit, we have
securely attached goggles, compass, and telescope.
Surprise Summer Adventure Coord!
Go!
Yeah!
One mustn't forget the treasure map,
so attach it to your waist...
as you wouldn't want to miss out
on the Summer Dream challenge.
Perfect Summer Adventure Coord!
The five who conquered an unforgettable adventure...
shall take on yet another one.
Unforgettable Summer Adventure Coord!
And that's all of our teams...
A team who just barely managed
to enter on time has just arrived!
We somehow made it in time-pri.
Yeah.
And here we have the newly formed Dream Team,
Dressing Flower!
Mirei, Sophy, I hope you're watching...
I'll just sing like myself.
Dream Theatre Concert, switch on!
Airy Change!
Cyalume Airy!
Thank you!
Tension max!
Relax!
Let's Go!
Let's ring the bell of everyone's dreams!
All of our dreams are united as one!
Ring out! Charm Bell!
There it is!
Somehow in their Cyalume Airy, they changed
into the Summer Dream Parade Coord!
Dressing Flower is our winner!
Of course they'd win-pri.
Toriko's idol won...
To... ri...
Kuma!
Usa!
Congratulations.
That was a wonderful concert.
Hey! We rang the bell, right?
Then doesn't that mean our wish will come true?
No, as you didn't ring
the Charm Bell of Beginnings in unison,
it will not grant your wishes.
What?
That's how the system works.
Isn't winning good enough?
We're all friends!
We're all idols!
I'll continue doing my best!
I'm Fuwari, and I'm from the Palps.
Fuwari of the Palps!
I'm turning down the princess candidacy.
You're making the wrong choice.
No, I've made up my mind.
My prince, I...
No, Hibiki, I don't really understand you.
But I'm still grateful.
Through trying to become a princess,
I learned a lot about PriPara, my precious friends,
and even how much my heart can ache.
I'll return to the Palps with these wonderful memories.
Good day.
Well, it was only natural.
She was but a mere a country girl, after all.
Playtime is over.
Andou, I wish to return home!
Prepare the car.
Right away.
And what shall I do with Celebrity 4?
Right. Them.
They were completely useless.
Send them back.
Right away.
What?!
"We're all friends"...
"We're all idols"...
You say?
How utterly absurd.
PriPara is about the best of the best.
There are far more beautiful places.
It seems that everyone's forgotten.
Only prodigies who possess
true radiance are fit to stand on stage.
To discern between those who
possess that and those who do not,
I shall reform PriPara.
Fuwari,
you are a failure.
Next time, I'll be taking it.
Midorikaze, what do you mean by "goodbye"?
I'm returning to the Palps.
You're kidding!
Pushuu...
Since I gave up being the princess candidate,
I no longer have a reason to stay here.
Why did you quit?
It's such a waste.
Baa baa.
Panda.
Both the goat and panda are sad.
Wait, panda?
Next time:
Genius? What's That-panda?
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!